<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- App Constants -->
    <string name="app_name">Daily Feats</string>
    <string name="internalDateFormat">yyyy/MM/dd-HH:mm:ss</string>

    <!-- Preference Keys -->
    <string name="currentFeatsLevelKey">current_feats_level</string>
    <string name="preferredHourKey">preferred_hour</string>
    <string name="preferredMinutesKey">preferred_minutes</string>
    <string name="setupCompleteKey">setup_is_complete</string>

    <!-- Layouts -->
    <!-- Universal -->
    <string name="save_only">Save</string>
    <string name="save_and_share">Save And Share</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="loading_message">Loading..</string>
    <string name="days_text">Days</string>

    <!-- Setup -->
    <string name="setup_name">Daily Feats Setup</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="setup_1_welcome">
        Welcome to Daily Feats.\n\n
    
        A small, simple application to help you keep track of your achievements
        on your road back from depression.\n\n
    
        First time setup takes about 2 minutes.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_2_question">
        Which of these statements most closely describes how you\'ve been feeling
        in the past two weeks?
    </string>

    <string name="setup_2_level_1">
        I frequently or sometimes don\'t get out of bed.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_2_level_2">
        I can get out of bed, but don\'t have the energy to do much else.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_2_level_3">
        I can get through the day, but I don\'t feel content.
        I feel like my life is missing something.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_2_level_4">
        I don\'t feel depressed right now, and I want to keep it that way.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_3">
        Freeing yourself from depression is in part about making an effort to
        keep track of certain important behaviors.\n\n

        We call each of those positive behaviors a "feat".\n\n

        Daily Feats will help you record and keep track of the feats you accomplish on a daily basis
        through the use of a simple daily checklist of goals.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_4_p1">
        Based on your answer to how you are feeling, Daily Feats will start you
        with the following list of goals:
    </string>

    <string name="setup_4_p2">
        Once a day, ideally at the end of the day, you will be asked to evaluate
        how many of these goals you completed that day.\n\n

        The purpose of completing this checklist is to give you an achievable set of goals to work
        towards, and to help you keep them in mind on a daily basis.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_5">
        You will also be given the opportunity to record a "Feat of Strength":
        something positive about the day that will help you remember it from any
        other day.\n\n

        Daily Feats will keep track of all of your feats. Both from your current list,
        and any Feat of Strength you enter, so that you can always look back and remind
        yourself of what you have achieved.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_6">
        Daily Feats will give you a reminder once a day to fill in your feats checklist.\n\n

        We think a good time for this reminder might be closer to the end of the day,
        perhaps an hour or two before bed time.\n\n

        The time for your daily reminder is currently set to:
    </string>

    <string name="setup_7">
        Daily feats will remind you at the selected time to complete your feats checklist.\n\n

        You can always change this time from the Application Settings Menu
    </string>

    <string name="setup_8">
        An important part of overcoming depression is staying connected to others.\n\n

        Daily Feats can, whenever you choose to do so, email a group of people with your
        day\'s successes.\n\n

        We recommend you choose a few (at least 1, at most 5) people from your contacts
        to form your group of supporters. They can be family, significant others, close friends, or anyone else you know.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_8_choose_supporters">Choose Supporters</string>

    <string name="setup_9">
        You can always update your list of supporters from the homepage.
    </string>

    <string name="setup_10_conclusion">
        Thank you for completing your first time setup of Daily Feats.\n\n

        We look forward to helping you on your journey to wellness, and beyond!
    </string>

    <!-- Complete Feats Checklist -->
    <string name="title_activity_complete_feats_checklist">Today\'s Feats Checklist</string>
    <string name="complete_feats_checklist_prompt">Today\'s Feats checklist</string>
    <string name="daily_FOS_label">Your Daily Feat of Strength</string>

    <!-- Home -->
    <string name="all_strength_feats_text">View all my Feats of Strength</string>
    <string name="no_feats_of_strength">No feats of strength, yet!</string>

    <!-- Temp -->
    <string name="completion_streak_placeholder">23</string>
    <string name="home_content_1">This is the home page</string>
    <string name="setup_content_1">Initial Setup Content</string>
    <string name="most_recent_feat_placeholder">I learned how to cut a pineapple!</string>
    <string name="feat_placeholder">Some Feat Label Placeholder ADD LOTS OF WORDS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_change_reminder">Change Reminder Time</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_feat_collection">Your List of Feats</string>

</resources>